artistaloud.com 2011-05-30

# Artist Loud

This Privacy Policy applies to the website titled  which is owned, operated, licensed and controlled by Hungama Digital Entertainment Media Private Limited (hereinafter referred to as " **Hungama** ", " **we** " and/or " **us** ") and is covered and protected by all laws including but not limited to copyright and trademark laws of India. 

**         

WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED ABOUT OUR USERS AND MEMBERS? 

**

The information that we collect about you while you are using the website falls into the following general categories.

**User provided information**

We may collect and store information, personal or otherwise, that you voluntarily supply either while on the website or in responding via email in connection with a feature provided on the website. Such information may include demographic information that you electronically submit when you sign up for access to certain features on the website, information (such as your name or email address or mobile number) that you electronically submit when you register for surveys or contests on the website, information that you post on message boards on the website, and information contained in search requests or questions that you submit to the website. If you decline to supply or provide us with certain information while using the website, you may not be able to use or participate in some or all of the features offered through the website. 

When you visit the  website, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser.  uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the website. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the website may not function properly.  
In addition, third party advertisers or third party ad servers that place and present advertising on the website also may collect information from you via cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies. These third party advertisers and ad servers may use the information they collect to help present their advertisements, to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness, or for other uses. The use and collection of your information by these third party advertisers and ad servers is governed by the relevant third party's privacy policy and is not covered by our privacy policy and we shall not be responsible for such third party's acts / use of such information. Indeed, the privacy policy of these third party advertisers and ad servers may be different from our privacy policy.

**Log file information**

When you use the  website, Hungama servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (" **IP** ") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

**Clear / Transparent GIFs information**

When you use the  website, we may employ "clear GIFs" (Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users / members anonymously. In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. 

**E-mail Communications**

To make e-mails more useful and interesting,  often receives a confirmation when you open e-mail from  if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Customer Communication Preferences. 

**Information from Other Sources**

might receive information about you from other sources and add it to your account information.  
[ **AZB Comment:** Please confirm, what information will be collected from the users.]

**HOW IS THIS INFORMATION USED?**

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the  website, we may use your personal information to operate, maintain and provide to you the features and functionality of the  website.

Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected, seen and used by others besides us. We cannot be and are not responsible for any unauthorized third party use of such information. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other users / members when you upload videos or send messages through the  website and other users / members can contact you through messages and comments. Any videos that you submit to the  website may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. [ **AZB Comment:** Please confirm]

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may provide our advertisers with information about you and other visitors that will enable our advertisers to better target ads to specific types of visitors. We reserve the right to use and to disclose to third parties all of the information that we collect online about you and other visitors in any way and for any purpose, with one important exception viz. We will not use the information that we collect online from you while you are using the website, nor will we authorize third parties to use such information, to mail or email promotional offers directly to you unless you have specifically informed us that you would like to receive promotional offers from us and/or from third parties. If you choose to receive these promotional offers, then your information may be used for direct mail or email marketing. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major  website changes or for customer service purposes). We may also make certain personal information about you available to the companies we have a strategic relationship with or that provide services to you on our behalf.

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, click stream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the  website and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user / member preferences and trends.

We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the  website; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, and contests.

The website includes links to other websites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase third party products or services through the website, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the website you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.

We may also make some content, products and services available through our website through cooperative relationships with third party providers, where the brands of our provider partner appear on the website in connection with such content, products and/or services. We may share with our provider partner any information you provide, or that is collected, in the course of visiting any pages that are made available in cooperation with our provider partner. In some cases, the provider partner may collect information from you directly; in which cases the privacy policy of the provider partner may apply to the provider partner's use of your information. The privacy policy of the provider partners may differ from ours. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of one of our provider partners, you should contact the provider partner directly for more information. Be aware that we may occasionally release information about visitors / members when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our terms of service agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of users of the website, the public, or the  website.

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that we sell some or all of our assets, or our website is acquired by another company, information about our visitors may be among the transferred assets.

**WHEN DOES   DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION?**

We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliate companies, or other businesses or people for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the  website.

We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with any law or to respond to a court order or an order from any governing body or statutory authority.

Hungama and  also reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that Hungama believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our 'terms and conditions of use', take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our website, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Hungama, , our users / members or others.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDRENS' PRIVACY**

The website is **NOT** directed to or **INTENDED** for individuals under the age of 18 (eighteen). An individual less than 18 (eighteen) years of age **SHOULD** not register to use the website but if you are above 13 (thirteen) years of age or older but below 18 (eighteen) years , you may be granted access by providing either of your parent's Email IDs and an Email will be sent informing the parent that their ward has registered himself / herself to use the Hungama services through the  website. If you are a parent of a child under the age of 18 (eighteen) and you have questions about our website or Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact the  Privacy Coordinator. Parent's of such underage individuals will be legally bound by any Acts / Deeds / Violation of  Terms and Conditions of Use, Privacy Policy and the end user license agreement. 

**OUR ASSURANCE & COMMITMENT TOWARDS DATA SECURITY**

Use commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information,  makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.   

If Hungama learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Hungama may post a notice on the  website if a security breach occurs. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify the  Privacy Coordinator.

**SPECIAL NOTE TO INTERNATIONAL USERS / MEMBERS**

Is registered in India. If you are a user / member accessing the  website from any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, user, protection and disclosure, that differ from the applicable Indian laws, please note that through your use of the  website, this Privacy Policy, end use license agreement and our Terms and Conditions of Use, you are transferring your Personal Information to India and you are giving a complete consent for the mentioned transfer. Hungama and  will, at any point of time, be complying with the legal provisions on the subject matter, as applicable in India from time to time.

**CHANGES TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION ON THE WEBSITE**

**Notification of Changes**

Hungama reserve the right at any time to: change the terms of this policy; change the services provided on the  website, including eliminating or modifying any content on or feature of the website; or change / charge any fees or charges for use of the services available on the website.

**Conflict Resolution**

Hungama is committed to resolving disputes as soon as feasible and shall endeavor to resolve all disputes brought to our notice in keeping with the mechanism prescribed.

**Access / Choice**

You may at any time modify your registration information by clicking on the "Edit Profile" subsection of the "My Account" area of the website, so long as you continue to provide us with certain information required to maintain your subscription (such as a valid email address). Also, marketing e-mails from  will come with instructions for un-subscribing from our email mailing list.
